<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Woodshop</title>
    <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:19:14 -0500</pubDate>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nesting Houses</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/nesting-houses</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Giltsoff </author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/nesting-houses</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bring a touch of the outdoors into your home with these Wood Nesting Houses from Hearth &amp;amp; Hand. This set of three simply designed wooden houses feature different shapes with window cutouts paired with a natural finish that&amp;rsquo;s both dynamic and versatile in style.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mug</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/mug</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 16:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Giltsoff </author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/mug</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Carved wood mugs are perfect for your morning cup of Joe or your afternoon pick-me-up! With its unique wood grain, no 2 mugs look exactly alike. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deer Teether</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/deer-teether</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 15:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Giltsoff </author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/deer-teether</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This chunky wood deer is nicely weighted and easily grasped, while the finely sanded wood makes them perfect for providing gentle counter pressure to sore gums. The beautiful embellishments are wood burned by hand offering a safe alternative to paints and dyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hardwood teethers are cut from maple and sanded smooth- once by machine and again by hand. Once sanded, each piece is polished with organic coconut oil.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookends</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/bookends</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 15:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Giltsoff </author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/bookends</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Style meets functionality in this adorable set of stained and painted mountain inspired wooden bookends! These are solid wood and stained with white &amp;ldquo;snow-capped&amp;rdquo; painted tops. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each half measures approximately 7&amp;quot;x4.25&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classic Coffeemaker</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/classic-coffeemaker</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 23:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/classic-coffeemaker</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Known as a pristine coffeemaker, Chemex employs all of the chemically correct methods for brewing. Its hourglass shaped flask is made entirely of glass, a chemically inert material that does not absorb odors or chemical residues. Includes a polished rubberwood collar with leather tie.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherry Graph Memo Book</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/cherry-graph</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/cherry-graph</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cherry Graph memo book by Field Notes features real cherry wood covers, filled with 48 pages of tried-and-true Finch Opaque Smooth 50#T with 48 pages of 3/16&amp;quot; graph paper inside.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Round Watch</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/round-watch</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/round-watch</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Designed in collaboration with Stefan Andrén and hand-assembled in Portland, Oregon. Watch features a hand sanded hardwood face, spherical hour markers, a precision calibrated stainless steel module, and a wrist strap of vegetable-tanned leather. Each watch is individually packaged and wrapped in distinctive heavyweight matte black paper and ready to gift. It’s an understated yet sophisticated method of keeping the time.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blocks &amp; Marbles</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/blocks-marbles</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/blocks-marbles</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Look forward to hours of creative maze-building. Handmade by Amish craftsmen in the heart of Indiana, each piece is meticulously inspected for quality. Wooden marble slides add an additional twist to tower construction. These are toys that will be handed down for generations. This set includes 45 hardwood blocks, 14 marbles and a sturdy canvas storage bag.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tie Bar</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/tie-bar</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 22:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/tie-bar</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Add a distinguished finishing touch to any look with these real wood tie bars. Each wood tie clip features a stainless steel body and real wood face that is hand selected for unique grain and quality. Also available in mahogany and walnut.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planter</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/planter</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 21:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/planter</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Each planter is carved from solid maple, lined with durable aluminum, and finished with a cork base. To feature the warmth of the wood, each planter is hand sanded then finished with a vegetable-based oil for a rich, lustrous finish. Perfect for all types of miniature flora. Also available in Walnut.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamp</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/lamp</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 21:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/lamp</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Crafted from solid walnut, each lamp is fitted with a brushed aluminum on/off switch and a durable woven cloth cord, then hand sanded and finished with a vegetable-based oil for a smooth, lustrous finish. Also available in Maple.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cube Speakers</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/the-cube-speakers</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 10:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/the-cube-speakers</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Machined from a solid beam of heart pine salvaged from a late 19th-century Virginia factory, the wood used is over 100 years old. Heart pine was used so extensively as the structural framework and flooring of typical American factories in the period that it was timbered almost to extinction. The demolition and salvaging and repurposing of these buildings is now the only manner to source this wood, a distinctly North American material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working with audio engineers, Fern &amp;amp; Roby designed the ported interior of the machined enclosure to be a “tuned” spatial volume to give the best bass response possible for a bookshelf speaker of this class. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Cruiser No. 6</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/mini-cruiser-no-6</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 10:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/mini-cruiser-no-6</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A super short cruiserboard suited to carving campuses, dropping curbs, and kicking up dust. Handcrafted with a vintage-inspired profile, rounded edges, and a beveled kicktail detail. Finished with love and two coats of marine grade varnish.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Butler</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/the-butler</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 13:33:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/the-butler</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This simple wall-mounted beauty keeps your keys, wallet, and glasses handy while charging your iPhone. Designed by Curtis Micklish and made with solid walnut and baltic birch laminated ply.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Campfire Cologne</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/campfire-cologne</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 12:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/campfire-cologne</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Campfire Cologne is the tried and true scent of your best summer ever. A nostalgic ode to cooking over the fire, secret swimming holes and the unending days of youth. Use it frequently, transport yourself, live the dream. Just &lt;a href=&quot;http://vimeo.com/47002032&quot;&gt;light it with the included matches&lt;/a&gt; and take in that sweet campfire scent, made with western red cedar.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belmont Sunglasses</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/belmont-sunglasses</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 23:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/belmont-sunglasses</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Made from sustainably-harvested wood, the Belmont&amp;rsquo;s refined aesthetic gives a nod to the past with its classic panto-shaped frame and distinct keyhole bridge. One of the slimmest pairs in the Shwood lineup, the Belmont offers clean, classic style with a modern twist.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Felling Axe</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/american-felling-axe</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 11:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/american-felling-axe</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Designed from the ground up in New York City by Best Made Company, tested the world over. The American Felling Axe has a 4lb Dayton pattern head, perhaps one of the most iconic American axe head designs, which is drop forged in the United States from an American-made 5160 alloy steel that is hardened to a Rockwell hardness of 54-56 HRC. The handle of the American Felling Axe is a straight-grain, premium hickory that originates in Appalachia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Blocks</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/christmas-blocks</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 23:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/christmas-blocks</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Designed by House Industries, these 14 embossed blocks spell “merry christmas” or &amp;ldquo;happy holidays&amp;rdquo; with the two embossed sides, one side painted green, the other red. The other sides are adorned with stacking trees designed with deliberately minimalist brush strokes creating a seasonal message celebrating Whoevillesque holidays where love and beauty outweigh consumer clutter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moonbeam Turntable</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/moonbeam-turntable</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 14:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/moonbeam-turntable</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When Ball and Buck went searching for the best American made audio equipment SOTA turntables quickly presented themselves as the absolute best in quality and design. The SOTA Moonbeam custom turntable, complete with bamboo casing is truly a unique piece for any home or office.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Ornament</title>
      <link>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/city-ornament</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 12:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>Skylar Challand</author>
      <guid>http://www.woodshopusa.com/products/city-ornament</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Celebrate the holidays with our 2013 Neighborwods ornament. Guaranteed to jazz up your tree, gift wrapping, or house. Comes in a keepsake canvas bag stamped with your city name, for easy gift giving and safe storage for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
